Delightful.
Heaven appears to be there after all.
And that place is at Cape Canaveral
Space Center, to be precise.
Hermes!
At the beginning of
everything, there was gravity.
What?
What's up with my hand?
Jolene.
Kujo.
Are you the friend who was
aiding Jolene in prison?
So if he punches us won't be in big trouble
that's why whenever his stance fists
make contact with something it'll be
inverted and I don't know how far but with
everything sideways we're just gonna
keep falling so this is it thanks to the
unique energy around Cape Canaveral the
priest has somehow developed a new stand
In order for human beings to attain happiness
they must first overcome their destiny
and the obstacles Dio and I must overcome
Are you damn Joestars in your bloodline?
Oh, shit!
Her heart has been turned inside out.
My phone!
But how?
It wasn't working before.
Could this text be from...
Jolene is alive.
But just barely.
Yeah, it is Mr. Jotaro.
He must be close by.
Anastasia, you've got to find Jolene!
I think that Jolene is still alive!
For real?
What's going on?
Jolene Kujo!
Her heart should have
been turned inside out!
I have to put an end to this!
The Joestar bloodline is something I
must overcome, no matter what it takes!
Which way are you going?
In order to protect Jolene, I'm gonna
have to kill that fucking priest!
I don't know.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
But all the future will
be the same as the fire.
The fire of the world will
Jolene, I'm well aware that she doesn't
have the capability to move her body.
But how is she still alive?
Did I somehow miss her
vital points by accident?
No.
Without a doubt, I hit her heart dead on.
It should have turned inside out.
Could this be the Joestar bloodline
and the blood of that damn Kujo?
Is that what's trying to hinder the plan
that Dio and I have
been working to achieve?
It's imperative that I end Jolene Kujo
here, no matter what lengths I must go to.
All of the times Jolene has
interfered with my plan,
within the prison and in Orlando,
have been tests on my path to heaven.
I know I can do this.
I'm Father Pucci.
I am the one who walks the
path with fate on my side.
Our plan goes beyond
petty feelings of justice.
Dio and I will succeed.
There isn't a soul in the world
capable of getting in our way.
It's simply inconceivable.
Hey, you there!
Please, help me!
I could really use a doctor!
I think my hip bone's pretty messed up.
Can you call an ambulance?
Please, don't leave me!
It is close.
I'm almost there.
The place where Jolene
fell should be around here.
She's there.
That's a scrap of Jolene's clothing.
Meaning it's likely that she wound
up falling into this building.
As for the fool sneaking up behind
me, I suggest you not come any closer.
Go away.
I do not consider you a test.
You don't even pose a threat to me.
Fall back, Seamoon!
That's not an Estacia!
Diver Drive can phase into more than
just walls in the ground, you know.
He was one of the tourists who
died from your gravity ability.
I changed his bone structure from
the inside and turned him into me.
And you're already within my range.
Take this!
Driver, drive!
I missed?
The madman.
He turned himself inside out.
To me,
your significance is
even less than Sun Wukong
as he bounced around in the Buddha's hand.
Something just touched my face.
That was Jolene Kujo's hand.
She's moving.
What on God's green earth is she doing?
How is she still able to move?
She's bleeding.
She must have suffered a grave injury.
My heart is telling me that I must
pursue her with everything I have.
Now is the time to end her permanently.
Given that he'll be
looking for his daughter,
I have no doubt that Jotro Kujo
will be arriving here any moment.
And it will be a real
nuisance if Anastasia regains
his composure and tries
to come for me again.
It appears that everyone is gathering to
this location in order
to protect Jolene Kujo.
If that is the case, what's most significant
right now is that you perish here.
They all believe in you,
but it is your death that will shatter the
hearts of everyone who
is heading this way.
Especially Jotaro will
be losing his daughter.
That should be enough to strip him of his
reason to live and the
strength in his heart.
He will no longer be a
threat to either me or Dio.
It has to be now, in this very place.
I will find you no matter what it takes!
Show yourself, Jolene and Cutter!
You can't hide anymore!
There you are, Jolene!
It's just her strings!
Damn it, she's behind me!
I am going to devote my entire being
to snuffing out your life right here!
I'm already aware you've
suffered a severe injury!
The gravity pulls in the opposite
direction of wherever my feet are!
Everything falls towards me!
Sea Moon!
There, I got you with a direct hit!
Now both of your arms are as good as gone!
What in the world was that?
Both of her arms should
have been inverted.
What the hell?
Come on out!
Now, Jolene Kujo!
Your attempts to stop me are futile!
You can't get away!
Holy Mother of God!
What is that?
What's that shape in her chest
where her heart should be?
Stone Ocean!
This is a Mobius Strip!
So that's what you're creating!
You start by tracing the
surface with your finger
and from there keep
going if you continue to
trace without ever lifting
your finger from the
surface you realize that
you've somehow ended up on
the other side but after
going around the entire
length of it you find
yourself back at the starting
point this shape with no
front side or backside
was discovered in the
19th century by a German
mathematician in honor of
him the shape was dubbed
the mobius strip in
order for it to invert it
would need more than one
surface but it has no
concept of inside or outside
the shape known as the
band of infinity she was
able to make one with
her thread but there's
only one possible moment
where she could have made
it and that's the very
moment when sea moon struck
her in the heart with
the first person to have
ever eaten a mushroom
has my respect it might
have been poisonous you
know was it just some
lucky fool that happened
to eat it and everything
turned out to be okay?
Or perhaps,
was it a final act of desperation fueled
by hunger that spurred this discovery?
Let's test a theory.
If you take a direct blow to your
brain, can you still stay alive?!
All I need is one.
But from which direction
shall I strike you down?
Just a single blow to your
head is all that it would take.
So that's it, huh?
If you're coming at me, you better
give it your all till the end!
Actually, I'm biding my
time for the perfect moment.
To assure my survival,
I've been observing you closely
as I circle around and corner you.
Waiting for the precise moment that
I shall finally achieve victory.
Do you understand what this means?
As I continue to walk
around you in circles,
all kinds of various objects will begin
falling into place in
the area surrounding me.
I just have to wait.
I'm waiting for my fated moment
of victory to gravitate toward me.
Do you see now?
With those dire wounds and
the Mobius Strip you've made,
Do you think you'll be able to avoid it?
It's here!
The moment I've been waiting for!
The corpse of the security guard!
And his gun!
Jolene!
Damn it!
Shit!
I can't do it!
Jolene, no!
Move, Jolene!
Raid!
What the? Hurrah!
Courtesy of the Speedwagon Foundation,
they fired the spear from three
kilometers up in the air and managed
to drive it straight into the
ground here at the Visitor's Center.
Using my stand smack,
I made it so the one spear split into two,
and when I peeled the sticker off, it
tried its best to come back together.
As long as I held on to the spear,
it still pulled me three
kilometers towards the other spear,
at an extremely fast rate,
regardless of gravity.
I used the same principle to get here
by dividing the spear a few more times,
all while following where he
sensed that Jolene was located.
Oh, man.
No!
Jotaro, Code, and Hermes
made it at the last second!
We've finally got you
surrounded, Father Keicho.
The idea that your stand
will reach its completed
state in 36 hours is just
your twisted fantasy.
This game is over.
You don't have any more
allies to help you.
And you won't ever be
able to see the new moon.
That's where you're wrong, Emporio.
It appears that fate...
Is truly on my side.
And is serving me with one last test.
To prove my worthiness.
What I thought was a hindrance.
Became exactly what I needed.
In the end, the Joestar bloodline.
Is here to lend me aid.
After my body was forcefully
thrown into this frame.
I finally saw the truth.
That the Kujos have been
my allies all along.
What is this?
Why the hell is that damn priest
floating up towards the sky?
As I said before, gravity is
working with me as its center.
I understand everything
now, Dio. This is it.
I no longer need to wait for the
new moon to arrive in 36 hours.
If what I require for this
to work is the gravitational
effect which is created
during the new moon,
then all I have to do is
stay afloat and keep rising
until I can discover those
exact gravitational conditions.
And from there, I'll have found it!
The spot with the same
pole as the new moon!
In order for my sea
moon to become complete,
there must be an optimal position
with which it'll activate!
You think we're gonna let you get away?
Keep struggling all you want, but
this is over for you, Poochie!
Relax your mind.
Locate the right position.
Calm down by counting the prime numbers.
Thirteen, seventeen, nineteen...
That son of a bitch is mumbling
something under his breath up there!
His gravity hasn't changed yet!
Everything's still being
pulled parallel to the ground!
Hey, Hermes, take a look at the ground.
Grab that gun he dropped earlier.
You've grown so much, Jolene.
Hold tightly to the railing.
Do it, Hermes!
Pick up that gun, and take the shot!
Seamoooon!
Stop time!
Start Platinum the World!
If I were a baton man, I'd say you're gonna
use your stand to deflect those bullets.
But time has been stopped
for a total of five seconds.
You won't even be able to
see this spear coming at you.
When time goes back to normal, that
spear will fly straight through you.
Three more seconds, two
seconds, one second.
Now time will resume.
What the hell just happened
the spear missed its mark.
He moved slightly during the time stop
It failed he's still alive
He's opening the door.
It looks like he's trying to
get inside the space shuttle
Yeah, and now this thing is
starting to float in the air, too?
The priest is taking shelter in
the goddamn display space shuttle!
He managed to avoid the spear.
But how?
It makes no sense.
Hey, you guys.
I don't think he's just
trying to get away.
It can't be. Did he?
Could he have discovered something
that's giving him the advantage?
Did he actually find the missing
element to complete his ability?
You are the ones who have been
helping to raise me up all along.
Ever since you were in prison, you
have been there, lending me aid.
Our Father who art in heaven, I
beseech you to lead and guide me.
I ask you to please watch over me, so
I may not walk down the wrong path!
It is to your very will that
I shall dedicate myself!
I can feel it!
The coordinates!
I'm here!
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here!
Although you think I smile,
Inside and all the while,
I'm wondering about my destiny?
I'm thinking
about all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer.
A distant dreamer.
Dreaming far away.
From today!
Thank you.